<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>The wheel of fortune: or, Nothing for a penny Being remarks on the dawing [sic] the penny-lottery, at the Theatre-Royal, in Dorset-Garden, with the characters of some of the honourable trustees, and all due acknowledgments paid to his honour the undertaker. Written by a person who was cursed mad he had not the thousand pound lot.</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1698</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 12 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 8 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2011-04">2011-04 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A65616</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Wing W1597C</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R221991</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">99833231</idno>
            <idno type="PROQUEST">99833231</idno>
            <idno type="VID">37706</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A65616)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 37706)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 2162:6)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>The wheel of fortune: or, Nothing for a penny Being remarks on the dawing [sic] the penny-lottery, at the Theatre-Royal, in Dorset-Garden, with the characters of some of the honourable trustees, and all due acknowledgments paid to his honour the undertaker. Written by a person who was cursed mad he had not the thousand pound lot.</title>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>[2], 10 p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>[s.n.],</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>printed in the year 1698. Price three pence.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>In verse.</note>
                  <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Lotteries --  England --  Poetry --  Early works to 1800.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2010-01</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-02</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-03</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-03</date>
            <label>Mona Logarbo</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-04</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:37706:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 119 -->
            <p>THE Wheel of Fortune: OR, <hi>Nothing for a Penny.</hi>
            </p>
            <p>BEING Remarks on the dawing the Penny-Lottery, at the THEATRE-ROYAL, in <hi>Dorſet-Garden,</hi> with the Characters of ſome of the <hi>Honourable Truſtees,</hi> and all due acknowledgments paid to his Honour the Undertaker.</p>
            <q xml:lang="lat">
               <l>—Momento turbinis exit,</l>
               <l>Macrus Davus,</l> 
               <bibl>Perſ.</bibl>
            </q>
            <p>Written by a Perſon who was curſed Mad he had not the Thou<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſand pound Lot.</p>
            <p>
               <hi>LONDON,</hi> Printed in the Year 1698. Price <hi>three pence.</hi>
            </p>
            <pb facs="tcp:37706:2" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 120 -->
            <gap reason="duplicate" extent="1 page">
               <desc>〈1 page duplicate〉</desc>
            </gap>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="poem">
            <pb facs="tcp:37706:3"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 121 -->
            <pb n="1" facs="tcp:37706:3"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 121 -->
            <head>THE Wheel of FORTUNE OR, <hi>Nothing for a Penny.</hi>
            </head>
            <l>
               <hi>DAme Fortune</hi> aſſiſt,</l>
            <l>If you pleaſe, or you liſt,</l>
            <l>Whilſt I ſing in the praiſe of a fancy,</l>
            <l>Which has gather'd the Croud,</l>
            <l>Rich, Poor, and Proud,</l>
            <l>From her Grace down to <hi>Suſan</hi> and <hi>Nancy.</hi>
            </l>
            <l>We ſhould do 'em much wrong</l>
            <l>Not to praiſe the dull Throng,</l>
            <l>And admire how the Devil ſo many</l>
            <l>Could venture together,</l>
            <l>In theſe ſharp <hi>times</hi> and <hi>weather,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>And all for one pitiful Peny.</l>
            <l>But the thing which in chief,</l>
            <l>Will ſuſpend our belief,</l>
            <l>
               <pb n="2" facs="tcp:37706:4"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 122 -->
Becauſe ſo uncommon and rare,</l>
            <l>Is that this happn'd out</l>
            <l>When the <hi>Rabble</hi> and <hi>Rout,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Should have paid their reſpects at <hi>Horn-fair,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>For the <hi>Cit</hi> was afraid</l>
            <l>Should he with <hi>Fork</hi> and <hi>Spade,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Like a true <hi>London Cuckold</hi> advance,</l>
            <l>Some more lucky Sot,</l>
            <l>Had march'd off with his Lot,</l>
            <l>And that was the Thouſand pound Chance.</l>
            <l>But no more of the Cits,</l>
            <l>If we're in our right Wits,</l>
            <l>And Reverence the <hi>Sword</hi> and the <hi>Mace,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>For Sir <hi>H—</hi> won't ſuffer</l>
            <l>Nor Flouter nor ſcoffer.</l>
            <l>Thoſe he's the chief of, to diſgrace.</l>
            <l>Wherefore let us proceed</l>
            <l>To give thoſe, who can read</l>
            <l>An account of the wiſe Undertaker,</l>
            <l>And as far as we dare</l>
            <l>Tho' the <hi>Cuckolds</hi> we ſpare,</l>
            <l>Make bold with the brisk <hi>Cuckold-maker,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>The Wheel's being plac'd</l>
            <l>And <hi>Lacker'd</hi> and grac'd</l>
            <l>Like a Chariot of Triumph or State,</l>
            <l>The Mob, Sir, and Gentry,</l>
            <l>At one time make their entry,</l>
            <l>And promiſcuouſly take each their place,</l>
            <l>Here <hi>Sarah</hi> and <hi>Moll</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Sit with <hi>Richard</hi> and <hi>Paul,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <pb n="3" facs="tcp:37706:4"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 122 -->
And a Perſon of Quality by 'em;</l>
            <l>Who with Hat lowring down</l>
            <l>Caſts many a frown</l>
            <l>Becauſe Sir, <hi>his Honour's</hi> ſo nigh 'em.</l>
            <l>But no matter for that</l>
            <l>They ne're mind his <hi>Hat,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>But keep gaping, and talking, and ſtaring</l>
            <l>Whilſt ſtate keeps the Lord,</l>
            <l>From ſaying one word,</l>
            <l>And much trys his Lordſhip's forbearing</l>
            <l>
               <hi>Look ye, <hi>Sarah,</hi> ſays <hi>Paul,</hi>
               </hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Our Old Maſter's Hall,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Is a booby to thick zame vine place;</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Zwounds, Girl, thick holds more,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Than his by zome ſcore,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>And looks in a much better caſe.</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Vaith, if yonder Dame Vortune,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Behind that zame Curtain,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Will a thouſand pound give for my Penny;</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Why, mun, Thee and I,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Shall have mony to buy</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>A Barn that will hold full as many.</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>I vow, and indeed,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>If I ſhou'd zucceed</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>We'd have <hi>Roaſt-meat,</hi> beſides upon <hi>Zunday:</hi>
               </hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>And e cod, Girl, a Witch</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>Said I ſhould be rich,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>As the <hi>Parſon</hi> himſelf ſhould be one day.</hi>
            </l>
            <l>When up flew the Curtain</l>
            <l>And ſhew'd Goddeſs <hi>Fortune,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <pb n="4" facs="tcp:37706:5"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 123 -->
Triumphantly plac'd on a Throne:</l>
            <l>Lord! how each beg'd and pray'd</l>
            <l>For her Ladiſhips aid!</l>
            <l>Tho' they had as well let her alone.</l>
            <l>For regardleſs ſhe ſate,</l>
            <l>'Midſt her Pomp and her State,</l>
            <l>Nor dar'd promiſe any her Favour,</l>
            <l>Whilſt a Goddeſs ſate by</l>
            <l>And with piercing eye,</l>
            <l>Obſerv'd her deſigns and behaviour.</l>
            <l>For the Deity Juſtice</l>
            <l>Sate over the <hi>Truſtees,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>And his <hi>Honour</hi> the noble Inventer,</l>
            <l>And upon my word,</l>
            <l>Her <hi>Scales</hi> and her <hi>Sword,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Would have been too hard for bad intent here</l>
            <l>Beneath Fortune that Goddeſs</l>
            <l>Stood one not over modiſh,</l>
            <l>With his Hat in his hand and beſeeching,</l>
            <l>That her Ladiſhip wou'd</l>
            <l>Uſe his words which were good,</l>
            <l>And his Prologue to make her ſpeech in.</l>
            <l>'Twas a Poet it ſeems</l>
            <l>With his Fancies and Dreams,</l>
            <l>But, Lord! what a figure he made!</l>
            <l>How he ſqueez'd when the Lady</l>
            <l>Was not over ready,</l>
            <l>And repeated not what he had ſaid!</l>
            <l>As the Prologue was ſpoke</l>
            <l>Without good ſence or joke,</l>
            <l>
               <pb n="5" facs="tcp:37706:5"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 123 -->
So a Lord of high Title and Birth,</l>
            <l>Firſt vow'd he was juſt,</l>
            <l>And in Sirs he thruſt</l>
            <l>The Tickets, which caus'd mighty mirth.</l>
            <l>Thoſe who were before ſad</l>
            <l>Look'd jocund and glad,</l>
            <l>Not doubting but right would be done;</l>
            <l>Since a Peer who laid claim</l>
            <l>To Honour and Fame,</l>
            <l>Swore all ſhould be paid that was won.</l>
            <l>For tho' we all knew</l>
            <l>'Twas certain and true,</l>
            <l>That the Tickets ſhould all be drawn out,</l>
            <l>Yet ſome were afraid</l>
            <l>They would never be paid,</l>
            <l>And at what time they will's yet a doubt.</l>
            <l>There was none but could read</l>
            <l>What his Lordſhip had ſaid,</l>
            <l>In the <hi>Majors</hi> boon Air and his Mein;</l>
            <l>For how could he do wrong,</l>
            <l>Who had ſuch a fine Tongue,</l>
            <l>And whoſe face, and whoſe hands were ſo clean?</l>
            <l>Tho' ſome who were there,</l>
            <l>Did not ſtick to declare,</l>
            <l>That his Honour was not a great Wit;</l>
            <l>Yet I vow and proteſt.</l>
            <l>Hes as wiſe as the beſt</l>
            <l>If they can ne'er be fooliſh who get.</l>
            <l>For what needed he mind,</l>
            <l>Whether Lame, Sick, or Blind</l>
            <l>
               <pb n="6" facs="tcp:37706:6"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 124 -->
The <hi>one Thouſand pound</hi> Ticket ſhould win;</l>
            <l>When all of us knew</l>
            <l>He himſelf would gain two,</l>
            <l>If I ſaid more it could be no ſin?</l>
            <l>In a cloſe Mourning ſuit,</l>
            <l>Majeſtick and mute,</l>
            <l>Like a true man of breeding he ſat.</l>
            <l>And would not ſo much</l>
            <l>As offend with a touch,</l>
            <l>The Mob, or his Wig, with his Hat,</l>
            <l>But a Doctor, whoſe head</l>
            <l>Was not ſo well bred,</l>
            <l>Cock'd his Felt to a Hair on his Crown;</l>
            <l>And ſwore 'twas not Law</l>
            <l>To be kept ſo in awe</l>
            <l>Of the ſcum of the Land, the Mob's frown.</l>
            <l>With his eyes on his noſe</l>
            <l>His worſhip aroſe,</l>
            <l>I ſhould ſay his Honour, for he,</l>
            <l>Tho' he's loſt all his places</l>
            <l>And at Court in diſgrace is,</l>
            <l>Has gain'd the name of a <hi>Truſtee.</hi>
            </l>
            <l>There's nothing that's evil,</l>
            <l>Said Man of Law-<hi>Civil</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Intended by ſmall or great Wheel,</l>
            <l>Can you think a Lord's Brother,</l>
            <l>Will do as another,</l>
            <l>Or Quality act any ill?</l>
            <l>By <hi>Digeſts</hi> and <hi>Codes,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>There are no greater Odds,</l>
            <l>
               <pb n="7" facs="tcp:37706:6"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 124 -->
Than one Thouſand eight Hundred to One,</l>
            <l>And that is not many,</l>
            <l>For a Lot's but a Penny,</l>
            <l>And I ſtand here to ſee Juſtice done.</l>
            <l>Can ye think, Sirs, one bred</l>
            <l>To write and to read</l>
            <l>As I, will paſs by a deceit?</l>
            <l>No, I'll lay a wager,</l>
            <l>His Honour the Major,</l>
            <l>Has not a bad thought in his Pate.</l>
            <l>Why Sirs, I am known</l>
            <l>To Country and Town,</l>
            <l>And have pleaded for Pirate and Thief,</l>
            <l>And tho' Judges and Jury</l>
            <l>Would not hear me, I aſſure ye,</l>
            <l>I can't but deſerve your belief.</l>
            <l>The folks could not ſay no,</l>
            <l>'Cauſe he made ſuch a ſhow,</l>
            <l>And was one of the <hi>fam'd Overſeers,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Tho' he might then have known</l>
            <l>What they thought would be done,</l>
            <l>Had his eyes but kept watch with his Ears.</l>
            <l>For thoſe who were told</l>
            <l>How clam'rous and bold</l>
            <l>He had been in his <hi>Advocate</hi>'s place,</l>
            <l>Thought his condeſcention</l>
            <l>To ſuch an Invention</l>
            <l>Had very much alter'd the Caſe.</l>
            <l>And, in troth, it was mean</l>
            <l>For him to be ſeen</l>
            <l>
               <pb n="8" facs="tcp:37706:7"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 125 -->
For a poor, ſorry, penny chance pleading,</l>
            <l>Who ne'er would make a plea</l>
            <l>Without a pound Fee,</l>
            <l>And very good drinking and feeding:</l>
            <l>But ſome who would excuſe,</l>
            <l>Said, he ought not to refuſe</l>
            <l>A Place of ſuch Honour and State;</l>
            <l>Since he would never lack,</l>
            <l>No good Fowls or good Sack,</l>
            <l>Which men of the Law never hate.</l>
            <l>But this may fuffice</l>
            <l>As the <hi>Pulpiter</hi> crys,</l>
            <l>Who nothing ſufficient has ſhown,</l>
            <l>For both I and you know,</l>
            <l>That <hi>Crimine ac uno</hi>
            </l>
            <l>The faults of the <hi>reſt</hi> may be known.</l>
            <l>The Lots and the Prizes</l>
            <l>Of all ſorts and ſizes,</l>
            <l>Being plac'd in the Wheels as deſign'd,</l>
            <l>A Boy at each Wheel</l>
            <l>Stood ready to feel</l>
            <l>If her Ladiſhip <hi>Fortune</hi> was kind.</l>
            <l>But me thought the Undertaker</l>
            <l>Made a mighty miſtake here</l>
            <l>In ſending for Boys from a place,</l>
            <l>As the houſe of Correction</l>
            <l>To give their inſpection</l>
            <l>In a thing of ſuch Grandure and Grace:</l>
            <l>For how could he ſuppoſe</l>
            <l>Any credit from thoſe</l>
            <l>
               <pb n="9" facs="tcp:37706:7"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 125 -->
Who are bred amongſt Thieves, and are taught</l>
            <l>To <hi>ſink</hi> and to <hi>palm</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Without any Qualm,</l>
            <l>And whoſe livelihood is to be nought.</l>
            <l>Tho' ſome thought it juſt</l>
            <l>That they ſhould have that truſt,</l>
            <l>As aggreeable to the plot laid</l>
            <l>For the Devil a bit,</l>
            <l>Did the Men of Wit,</l>
            <l>If they <hi>won</hi> believe they ſhould be <hi>paid.</hi>
            </l>
            <l>The fair Mrs <hi>Wiſe</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Got the Fortunate prize.</l>
            <l>If <hi>Poſt-boys</hi> and <hi>Poſt-men,</hi> are true,</l>
            <l>Tho' what ſhe'll receive</l>
            <l>Gentle Readers I leave</l>
            <l>To ſuch <hi>Politicians</hi> as you.</l>
            <l>This I am ſure of, that ſhe</l>
            <l>May have you, him, or me,</l>
            <l>If they juſtly and honeſtly pay her,</l>
            <l>For a Thouſand pound Sterlin</l>
            <l>Will make any Girl in</l>
            <l>The Kingdom, ſucceed in her prayer?</l>
            <l>But have it or not,</l>
            <l>She'll ne'er like ſuch a ſot</l>
            <l>As the Perſon who writing now is,</l>
            <l>For it is his damn'd fate</l>
            <l>Neither ſplay-foot nor ſtrait,</l>
            <l>E're yet fell in love with his Phiz.</l>
            <l>Wherefore <hi>Fortune</hi> and <hi>Juſtice</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <hi>
                  <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>ndertaker</hi> and <hi>Truſtees,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>
               <pb n="10" facs="tcp:37706:8"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 126 -->
And Caſhiers and Bankers adieu,</l>
            <l>For it is but fitting</l>
            <l>There ſhould be ſome greeting</l>
            <l>At parting between me and you.</l>
            <l>I have no more to ſay,</l>
            <l>If you will you may pay,</l>
            <l>If you wo'nt you may take to your heels,</l>
            <l>For, Zouns I have loſt</l>
            <l>Ev'ry Jack, to my coſt,</l>
            <l>And along with your damn'd Wheels.</l>
            <trailer>FINIS.</trailer>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
